regfox.com 2014-12-20

# Webconnex Privacy Policy

Webconnex respects your privacy and works hard to safeguard the privacy of your personal data as you have provided it. We realize that the rapid growth of the Internet and online services raises questions concerning the nature, use and confidentiality of information collected about consumers. We want you to know that we apply our commitment to safeguarding privacy to our online and Internet activities. 

Personally Identifiable Information 

Webconnex provides “merchants” with web based software that collects payment details and customer information from its customers and participants. In order to process online payments and provide service to merchants, Webconnex asks for personally identifiable information (such as your name, address, city, state, zip) from you in order to complete the transaction, registration or payment. Webconex only discloses personally-identifiable information to the merchant in accordance to the merchant’s requirements. Webconnex does not share any information with unaffiliated companies or organizations. Because data submitted through Webconnex is a critical part of our business, it would be treated like our other assets in the context of a merger, sale or other corporate reorganization or legal proceeding. 

How We Use Information 

Webconnex uses the personally-identifiable information we collect online principally to provide you with the service(s) of registering for an event online, making an online donation, subscribing to a newsletter or otherwise registering for an online form. Postal and e-mail address information, for example, enables communication about services/items offered and ordered, as well as the proper provisioning and billing of those services (e-mail sales receipts, for example). Webconnex may involve other companies or vendors to carry out certain functions in marketing and delivering services to you (such as processing data files and sending you new order fulfillment information), and so may share data with those vendors to the extent necessary for them to perform their work. Of course, such partners and vendors must use that personally-identifiable information only for the purpose(s) for which it was shared and protect it from any further use. 

We also provide personally-identifiable online information in response to subpoenas and other legal demands, and where we believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against individuals who may be endangering public safety or interfering with Webconnex property or services, or with our customers' or others' use of them. 

How We Collect Information 

Webconnex collects information principally online upon signup of Webconnex as a merchant and any registration form through any of the Webconnex products created by the merchant. For example, when you order a product, take a survey, make a donation, or to submit to contest, or other promotion from our merchant, we capture this information on behalf of our merchant. A customer's name, address (postal and e-mail) and telephone number are usually asked for in these cases, but we might request other information, based on the services involved from the requirements of our merchant. We do not share, make data or personally identifiable information of participants of merchant available to any third party for any reason. 

Webconnex may also use "cookies" and similar technology to obtain information about your visits to our sites or your responses to e-mail from us - both individually and in aggregated data that does not identify you. These reporting tools tell us the parts of our web sites or e-mails in which you showed an interest or took some action, and help us improve the quality and usefulness of our sites. 

Security 

We use encryption, firewalls and other technology and security procedures to help protect the accuracy and security of your personal information and prevent unauthorized access or improper use. For example, you will note that while using some features of the Webconnex web site and online services, you may need to submit a password or some other type of authenticating information. All online sales procedures (for example member subscriptions or e-store purchases) are processed through our 256-bit SSL secure server. 

Webconnex may use e-mail addresses of merchants who signed up online to send an e-mail related to our products and if affirmatively indicated a desire to receive additional information. If at any time, you would prefer not to receive further e-mail communications at that e-mail address, please contact Customer Service through the number or e-mail address listed below. 

**For questions regarding this policy, contact:**

Webconnex Customer Service  
455 Capitol Mall Suite 325  
Sacramento, CA 95814  
888-317-4539
